Your fairy friend. In order to determine
where your silver sugar was.
He had to give
his wing to Bridget.
His wing? He sold his freedom to
make sure you'd be all right.
And what happened?
Oh. Poor thing. Sorry.
I guess the shock was too much.
You weasel!
Tell us what you did.
You hand it over Charles Wing.
He was with you.
How could you have let
something like that happen?
You make it sound like
I did something evil.
And Silver sugar was returned.
So it's all right.
And the price
to get it back was.
Shall he and Bridget did
all of the negotiating,
so it wasn't like
I was heavily involved.
I can't believe how
badly I misjudged you.
Hold on. You're leaving?
Mr. Angley.
Why did she go this far?
Just to help me?
Even if I had failed,
there'd still be next year.
Sorry, but. I think it's
because of something I told him.
Everyone's too jealous of her.
There was last year's contest.
Then all that business involving
the former Duke of Phylax.
This was your final
chance to win the title.
You wouldn't be able to get
Silver Sugar for next year.
That was what I sent to shell.
I've been.
Oblivious to everything.
Then. All right, then we need
to get to the workshop
so you can talk some sense
into that girl. Hmm.
You're right.
Let's go in. And don't
worry. I'll be with you to.
Thanks. You too. Really?
Actually, she's not there.
She's at Millfield. Specifically the main
location for the page workshop.
Are you kidding me?
I'm not. See?
Look, we got a letter that said
Mr. Glenn hasn't
been doing well.
Mr. Glenn.
The master of the page school.
That's why she rushed back home.
Sorry.
You just missed her.
It can't be.
In any case, now that I've
gotten forgiveness from Master Radcliffe,
I believe I'll return
to Mills Field myself.
Mr. Glenn's health
is important to me.
Care to join you?
Might as well. Right. Mm.
You're a silver sugar
master now, remember?
So if you came to work with
us at the page workshop,
then perhaps I could
use that leverage
to create an opportunity
for you to get
your furry friend back
from Brigittes clutches.
How does that sound to you?
And why do that? Why help?
I don't know,
but he's obviously
plotting something foul.
Plotting? Don't be ridiculous. Can't I do
something nice for a friend.
If I do? Does that mean that I'm
affiliating myself with
page officially? That it does.
Very well. Thomasville. Then an you should
think about it more carefully.
He is bound to have
a secret motive.
It might be something
that you'd regret.
Cells there.
So that's where I want to go.
And yes,
if you're seriously offering me
a position at the page workshop.
Then it would be
my honour to accept it.
How wonderful.
I'm glad you see it
that way. Took you long enough.
Are you finished packing? Yes. We'll
leave in the morning. Right.
Mhm. You look upset.
You're scared aren't you.
But I admit I do understand
the way he must feel.
He made his own choice Anne.
Don't feel bad about it.
Thanks for that. But either way,
I still want to rescue him.
I want him to be free. Knowing
Xiaofan, shall I bet he'll say
I never asked you to save me?
Probably so.
But still, I have to
do something. It's for me to.
Hmm'hmm. I see. In that case,
let's go and get him back.
But first we should have
a nutritious meal.
Never fear, for I shall
procure it with ease. Ah, ah.
Thanks so much.
So he's the one
who gave me this. Huh?
Are our shiny new
silver sugar master. You.
You needed to speak with me?
Yes.
I assume you know the cat despises
me with a passion, right?
Oh, I wouldn't say. Don't worry.
I've known forever.
He feels that way.
Surprisingly,
that same cat paid me a visit.
He said he had a favor to ask
of me. And it was about you.
About me.
Indeed, he wants me to use
my authority as the Silver
Sugar Viscount
to retrieve shell from the
daughter of the page workshop.
Since Kat was in charge
of manufacturing the sugar,
he seems to feel responsible
for this matter.
He shouldn't.
This isn't Kat's fault at all.
That's what I said to him.
The problem is,
like a certain other person,
I know he's caring to a fault.
Now, an it's feasible
for me to pressure
the page workshop and they would
let Xiao go without a word,
but that would be rather
high handed of me.
Yes, I know. Please don't do
that, Hugh. It's far too much.
I'm grateful Kat feels that way.
But if I don't
atone for my foolishness myself,
there's no point.
So I'm going to rescue Shel without
relying on someone else's help.
If I don't, then the Royal
medal he gave me means nothing.
And I'm not a real
silver sugar master.
Hmm. It looks like I win.
When? What?
I told Kat when I talked to you,
that you would say
something along those lines.
Even then, he wouldn't
back down. So I decided
we should make it a wager.
He bet you'd want me to get
involved.
And I bet you wouldn't.
And now that he's lost,
the penalty
is that I have a chance to force
him to do anything I say. He.
Really anything.
Now what shall I get him to do?
I wonder if he cries.
Then that's even better. You
tormenting him has been
a hobby of mine
for as long as I've known him.
Don't stop me.
It's in poor taste. I can't.
Resist it.
He gets so mad and fussy.
Teasing
him is endlessly fun for me.
An. You're serious about
getting Shao back? Yes.
Hmm.
For the next year, you'll have
to work hard to establish
yourself as a master.
It is a crucial time.
If you stumble now,
people will claim you
didn't deserve the Royal
Medal,
especially since you're a woman.
The eyes of the world are harsh.
Then again, if you're
still resolved to rescue Chao,
it's your first step to calling
yourself a silver sugar master.
I'll get him
back no matter what.
It's just me and a cute girl
all alone. My heart's a flutter.
Wait a minute.
Why did you have to come along?
And what do you mean, alone?
I'm here to remember.
Oh, right, I forgot. And a fairy
to wait on us.
You take that back immediately.
Putting that aside,
is Chale your lover or what?
No, it's not like that at all.
So it's one sided. Oh,
you poor thing. Ah! We're here.
The page workshop is made
up of all the buildings
you see there.
And you are. Hello. Mr.
Elliott Collins invited me, sir.
I'll be working here at page
soon. My name is Anne Halford.
Oh, is that so? And you are?
Ah. I see you've met our guest.
What is all this? Who? She.
Anne Halford,
this young lady is a silver
sugar master.
I found her in Lewiston.
She has a medal.
Isn't she just adorable?
And she'll be employed
with us starting
tomorrow.
You'll play nice, won't you?
What's this problem?
His name is Orland Langston,
our head of artisans here.
He's got skill.
We're the same age, but he's
a lot less friendly than me.
Well, are you ready to go?
I'm here. This is the girl
I told you about, Mr. Glenn.
Huh? My name is Glen page, miss
and I serve as the master
of the page workshop.
It's a pleasure.
My name is Anne Halford.
Just as I thought. You're
a tiny and frail little girl.
But then, perhaps
that is all the more reason.
I'm sorry to greet you from bed,
but I have a heart condition.
So you've earned a Royal Medal.
That's no easy feat.
Now that you're
a silver sugar master,
are you certain
that you'd be willing
to come and work for us?
The smallest of all the schools?
Yes, sir.
Is this about the fairy that
Bridget brought here yesterday?
That's right.
He and I have traveled
together for a long time.
So tell me.
If you were to accept
employment with us,
would you give
it your best effort?
I never cut corners in my work,
sir. I'll give it my all.
Very well, then. If that's the case,
you'll begin working here tomorrow.
Father, wait. Are you sure
that's what you want? Yes, but.
She's a woman, the same as me.
Remember what you
told me long ago?
A girl can never become
a sugar artisan.
Your own daughter
wasn't allowed. And you're
going to hire her over me?
As the daughter of a headmaster,
such
a thing would be
impossible for you.
That fact isn't going to change.
Are
we clear? I said, are we clear?
Yes. I didn't realize Miss Bridget wanted
to become a sugar artisan.
I don't understand why
is it all right for me,
but not for
Mr. Paige's daughter?
Please excuse her.
Now, about your job.
I'm going to put you in charge
of overseeing all
the other workers as our
head of artisans.
How does that sound?
Ordinarily,
I would have Elliot handle that,
but currently he's serving as our
representative in official matters.
Yes, I see, but shouldn't
it be Mr. Orland? Orland?
You're a silver sugar master,
so it would be unthinkable
for you to work
under someone who isn't.
You should be the one who
presides over all the artisans.
But, sir, it's so sudden. I only
received the Royal Medal yesterday.
But you do have it. Which means
that working
as a silver sugar master
is not only natural for you,
it's required. Oh.
So if I turn away from this,
I don't deserve
to hold the Royal Medal.
Understood.
Then, from now on, I'm the
head of artisans here at page.
I'm glad to have you. From the
way Elliot has described you,
you seem like
the first silver sugar.
The first silver sugar. Elliott would
explain it better, of course.
On the subject of your ferry.
I've all reason
to believe that you'll
work hard and become
a great asset to our workshop.
If that is the case,
then I'll give him back.
Will you rather know
that ferry belongs
to me now? So you can't.
You forget you are the daughter
of this school's founding family.
One day you will be wedded
to Elliott
and the workshop will
become yours to own.
This girl's ferry has
no place in your future.
And even if he is a ferry,
I'd rather not have him by your
side. Since you're marrying me,
Elliott.
It's not fair. This is my life,
you know. That may.
Be. But tell me
whose daughter you are.
Yes I know.
I am the daughter of Glen Paige.
I understand that, but.
I refused to give
him back to that awful girl.
Ah. I'm sorry. That was shameful.
I don't mind, sir. Truly.
They're horrible.
Both Elliot and my father.
The workshop is all
anyone thinks about.
No one ever considers what
I might want to do.
They're always so selfish.
It makes me sick.
That's immature.
I can't believe Elliot
brought an Alford here,
but I bet you're happy.
I know you are
and is going to work here. And
if she does a satisfactory job,
then my father said that he would
give your wing back to her.
This is great news. And you can
rescue shall and shall now.
If this works out for you,
I will be grateful
as well.
My actions did hurt you.
When Bridget and Xiao
were negotiating all this,
I thought that the deal was necessary
to locate the silver sugar.
But I was also hoping
to leverage it somehow.
What if Xiao ended up here? Then
I figured it was a safe bet
that Anne would follow him.
You dare deceive me?
Does that mean
you did all of this
to get me to work here?
Sorry for the foul play.
But why did you need me?
I have hope. In what? Not just
in your skills
as a silver sugar master.
It's hope that. Something new
might happen with. You around.
In more ways than one. The page
workshop. Is too earnest.
Elliot, does it have
something to do with what
Mr. Glenn said about
the first silver sugar?
There's no way she'll succeed.
She only
became a silver sugar master
yesterday. What can she do?
With that in mind, you will
continue to belong to me,
even if Ann is working here.
From now on. I'm ordering
you never to see that girl.
If you do, you'll be punished.
Look in. There. It's him.
I'm sorry.
I never intended to make you suffer.
Just don't see her. Ever.
Oh, show.
And you seriously do
love that fairy,
don't you?
That makes me jealous.
For as long
as I've known Bridget,
she's never felt that way
about me. Even a little.
Bit. What?
Really? Then why are you engaged
to her?
Because Mr. Glenn desires it.
Yes, but. We have
an understanding. If it is his
wish, then that's enough for us.
You're really all right with it.
Your question cuts
me to the quick.
I'm glad you're that way.
That's why I'm so hopeful.
This is the workshop building.
But there's no one here.
I suppose they're not back yet.
You mean the other artisans,
right? I believe
they all went out
to do some sugar refining.
This is different from the
Radcliffe workshop, isn't it?
Where? A smaller operation.
This here is the main workshop.
But if you counted me
or Linde and the others.
We're only a team of five.
Only five of you
and no apprentices?
None at all.
There are some fairies
who helped maintain the main
building. But that's it.
I see, but for artisans.
Just five.
Yes, that's right. I think that should
be a pretty clear indication.
We just don't have
enough artisans. So we're
in kind of a tricky spot here.
Uh, it caused a noticeable decrease
in our sugar confection orders.
Like I said before, I have high
hopes you can help us fix it.
So, um. Good luck. Thank you.
How can I rebuild this workshop
with only five
artisans working here?
Huh?
Ah, so it's you.
I saw you through the window. Don't
strut around in your nightgown.
Oh. You're right.
Wait just a moment.
What happened? I heard
about the silver sugar, so I.
Made the decision myself.
It doesn't concern you.
Actually. Well, it does.
You should leave, I won't.
I'm going to free you
from this no matter what.
You idiot! Turn and face me!
I told you.
Oh. Thanks for that.
I want to stay with you
and with me through Lilypond
as well. All of us together.
You'll adjust to this.
It's fine, but.
I don't want to adjust.
That's childish.
If that's the only reason you're here,
then leave. That isn't all.
The truth is,
I have to rescue you, shell.
Or else I can never
say that I became
a silver sugar master
by my own strength.
By your own strength?
If nothing changes,
then I'll have earned the title
because of your strength.
That's why I'll rely
on my own abilities.
What I can do as a sugar
artisan to set you free shall
if I succeed.
And someday I can proudly.
Say I'm a silver sugar master.
My team.
You're truly very stupid.
No, don't call me stupid.
I made the mistake. If you say
this is a matter of pride for
you. And I won't stop you. And.
I've never
been rescued by anyone.
You say that you're going
to save me from this?
So what should I do?
Just tell me.
You're the one being saved,
so I don't
think you need to do anything.
As long as you'll wait for me.
If you tell me to wait, I will.
Then please wait. As you wish.